-I wait.  -Enjoy your visit.
-我等着  -旅途愉快
Next.
下一位
-Officer Torres.  -Mr Navorski.
-桃乐丝小姐  -纳沃斯基先生
You have choose.
让你选择
Man with money or man with love?
有钱的男人还是有爱的男人?
What is choose?
你选什么?
She had a boyfriend?
她有男朋友了?
-For how long? -Two years?
多久了?二年了?
What happened?
到底发生什么了?
He chit.
他是"屎"
-What?  -He chit.
-什么?  -他是"屎"
-Eat shit?-He chit.
吃屎? 他是"屎"
He chit. He chit. He chit.
他是"屎" 他是"屎" 他是"屎"
-Repeat exactly what she said.  -He chit. She catch him. So...
-说得准确点  -他"屎" 被她发现了 所以
-He cheats.  -Yes.Yes.Yes.Yes.
-他是骗子  -是的,是的,是的,是的
What we call krushkach. We say krushkach.
我们叫做"脚踩二条船"
One man, two womans.
一个男人 二个女人
So. Mm.
所以
Crowded, you know.
太拥挤了 你知道吗
OK. He cheats.
好的 他是个骗子
-You say "cheats".  -He chit.
-你说"骗子"  -他是"屎"
no .no .No, "cheat".  -Enrique.
-是"骗子"  -对  对
You, no chit.
你不能"屎"她
-No cheat.  -No chit.
-不要欺骗她  -不要"屎"她
-No cheat to her. -Yeah,Yeah,I won't.I won't.I won't cheat.
不要欺骗她。不 我不会骗她。
-Not chit.-She's a nice girl. She won't take your chitting.
不是“屎”。她是个好女孩 她不会上你的当